export const quizes = [
  {
    question: "HTML can be used to build a website on its own",
    answer: true,
  },
  {
    question: "HTML is the only markup language in existence",
    answer: false,
  },
  {
    question:
      "There is no difference between block elements and inline elements",
    answer: false,
  },
  {
    question: "CSS can be used as an alternative of HTML",
    answer: false,
  },
  {
    question: '"div.my-div > h1#main-header" is a valid CSS selector',
    answer: true,
  },
  {
    question: "HTML 3 is the current version of HTML",
    answer: false,
  },
  {
    question: "Java is anaother name for JavaScript",
    answer: false,
  },
  {
    question: "JavaScript is a programming language",
    answer: true,
  },
  {
    question: "myNumber /= 4 is not the same us myNumber = myNumber/4",
    answer: false,
  },
  {
    question:
      "With JS, I can remove or and add HTML and CSS dynamically to my site",
    answer: true,
  },
];
